因此我们可以肯定 你在一天中哪个时间点做这项测试将影响你的So definitely, the time of day that you took the test could have influenced your
记忆力表现 如果你在晚上进行这项测试 也许你会很疲惫而影响结果memory. If you're taking the test late at night, you might be really tired, or
或许你的大脑没有早上清醒 就像我朋友一样 他maybe your brain just doesn't work in the morning, like one of my friends. He
早上脑子就不好使 而这并不是说时间一定会can't think at all in the morning. That isn't to say that it definitely did
影响你的记忆力 而是也许会影响 夏威夷的棕榈树数量 influence your memory, but it could have. The number of palm trees in Hawaii
并不会影响你的记忆力 你的压力水平isn't very plausible to have influenced your memory. Your stress level
一定会影响到你的记忆力 如果你压力非常大 也许definitely could have influenced your memory. If you're really stressed, maybe
可能你就记不住了 牛奶的价格 不太可能 五分钟的you don't remember as well. The price of milk, not so plausible. The five minute
休息时间？ 当然了 如果你不休息五分钟 我估计breaks? Absolutely. If you didn't take the five minute breaks, my hunch is that
想把 part1 和 part2 的脸区分开来会更难 it might be more difficult to remember which face was from part 1 or part 2. The
冥王星的质量 不太像 你的年龄？ 当然了 最后 注意力 Mass of Pluto, not so much. Your age? Definitely. And finally, not paying
不集中 当然会影响你的记忆力 所以这项 BBC 研究 attention, definitely could have influenced your memory. And the BBC study
得出结论 年龄和做测试的时间是影响人们记忆力测试 concluded that age and time of day were the two biggest influencers on how well
最大的两个因素 如果你没能看到这项 BBC 测试 people performed on this memory test, if you didn't get a chance to see the BBC
test results. So, we're looking at a bunch of different things that could have
的结果 因此 我们参考了许多不同的可能
影响记忆力的因素 包括睡眠 我们总在假设 influenced your memory, including sleep. We make hypotheses all the time,
每天如此 everyday.